All right, so open up the NumbersActivity.
打开 NumbersActivity
And let's start here by detecting the click on the list item.
从这里开始 检测列表项上的点击操作
So what we'll need to do is temporarily hook it up to play a toast message so
我们需要做的是暂时将其与提示消息绑定了
that we know that our code is working.
以便知道我们的代码可以运行
So scrolling down here, this line,
往下滚动到这行
listView.setAdapter, is where we bind our word adapter to our listView.
listView.setAdapter 我们会在这行将我们的 WordAdapter 与 listView 绑定
So after this line would be a good place for us to configure our onClickListener.
在这行之后可以配置我们的 onClickListener
So we'll use a listView object and call the setOnItemClickListener method on it.
我们将使用 listView 对象并对其调用 setOnItemClickListener 方法
And when it showed up with the autocomplete suggestions,
当它从自动填充建议中出现时
I clicked Enter.
按下 Enter
Now here only to pass in an OnItemClickListener.
这里我们需要传入 OnItemClickListener
Now since this is an interface, we have to implement the method ourselves.
因为这是接口 我们需要自己实施方法
So here, since we're only writing one method, it's easy for
这里我们仅写了一个方法
us to implement it in line right here as an anonymous class.
所以很容易在行内直接实施为匿名类
However, if we were to define many methods,
但是 如果我们定义了多个方法
we would probably want to define it all in a separate class file and
我们可能需要在单独的类文件里定义每个方法
then just call the classes constructor in here.
然后在这里调用类构造函数
So to begin writing our anonymous class,
要开始写我们的匿名类
I'm going to type in here new OnItemClickListener.
我在这里输入“new OnItemClickListener”
So Android Studio is giving me an autocomplete suggestion, so
Android Studio 给出了自动填充建议
I'm going to select that suggestion.
我选择该建议
And with it, Android Studio knows that we need to find an OnItemClickListener
根据该建议 Android Studio 知道我们需要寻找一个 OnItemClickListener
and override the onClick method.
并重写该 onClick 方法
So instead of onItemClick method, let's just pop up a toast message temporarily.
我们暂时先弹出一个提示消息 而不是使用 onItemClick 方法
I'm going to call Toast.makeText and pass in a context and
称之为 Toast.makeText 传入一个 Context
remember that our activity is a context.
注意我们的 Activity 是个 Context
So normally, we can refer to the class that we're inside.
通常 我们可以引用我们所位于的类
So the one here in NumbersActivity as just this.
在 NumbersActivity 中可以使用 this
But in certain places such as inside the OnItemClickListener,
但在某些位置 例如 OnItemClickListener 内
using just the word this can become ambiguous.
使用单词 this 会比较模糊
So here we specify the class first, so we have NumbersActivity.this.
所以这里 我们先指定类 即 NumbersActivity.this
Now, the second input of the toast message is to display what we want
提示消息的第二个输入值为显示我们想在屏幕上
to see on screen.
看到的内容
So here, let's have it display list item clicked and
这里 我们让其显示“List item clicked”
for the third input we specify the duration of the toast.
对于第三个输入值 我们指定提示消息的时长
So here, let's have it display for a short period of time.
这里 我们让其显示很短的时间
The output of the makeText method call will be a new toast object.
makeText 方法调用的输出值将为新的 toast 对象
So following that we can call the show method on that.
在此之后 我们可以对其调用 show() 方法
Now let's run the app on our device.
现在在设备上运行下应用
So let's tap into the NumbersActivity and then type in a list item.
点按 NumbersActivity 然后点按某个列表项
Nice, so our toast is working.
不错 可以显示提示消息
Now, let's modify the behavior so that clicking on a list item
现在来修改下该行为 点击列表项后
plays an audio file instead of popping up a toast message.
会播放音频文件 而不是弹出提示消息
So first, I downloaded the audio file, which was provided for you in the quiz.
首先 我下载了音频文件 我在测试题中为你提供了该文件
I'm going to copy and paste that, and back in Android studio,
复制该文件 回到 Android studio
I created the raw folder in the resources directory of the app.
我在应用的资源目录下创建了 raw 文件夹
So inside that, I'm going to paste in the audio file.
我将刚才的音频文件粘贴到该文件夹内
So the default name that we have is okay and
我们可以保留默认的名称
now the audio file is included in our app.
现在音频文件已经包含在我们的应用中了
Now, let's focus on the NumbersActivity and how to play that audio file.
我们先重点研究下 NumbersActivity 看看如何播放该音频文件
We know that we'll need a media player object instance.
我们知道我们需要 MediaPlayer 对象实例
So let's declare a new member variable in this activity.
我们在这个 Activity 中定义一个新的成员变量
Now we can either go back to the tutorial that we used for
我们可以回到 MediaPlayer
the MediaPlayer app, or
应用的教程
we can go back to the first article here that we saw on the Media Playback.
或者回到我们看到的第一篇关于 Media Playback 的文章
Now, either would work.
二者都可以
So here we can copy this code that creates a new MediaPlayer object for
我们可以复制这段代码 即为某个原始声音文件创建
a certain raw sound file.
一个新的 MediaPlayer 对象
Now let's go back to our app in Android Studio.
现在回到  Android Studio 中的应用
Now within the onItemClick method, let's remove this line
在 onItemClick 方法中 我们删除这行
that shows a toast message and instead paste in the media player code.
显示提示消息的代码 并粘贴 MediaPlayer 代码
So we need to make some modifications to this code.
我们需要对该代码做出一些修改
So here we don't need to define the media player object data type again,
这里我们不需要再次定义 MediaPlayer 对象数据类型
instead we can just refer to the global variable that we called mMediaPlayer.
可以直接引用称为 mMediaPlayer 的全局变量
So we'll need to also update all the references to
我们需要将所有指代变量名称 MediaPlayer 的地方
the variable name MediaPlayer with mMediaPlayer.
更新为 mMediaPlayer
Now, there are a couple more errors.
这里有几个错误
So here the variable context is not recognized.
这里的变量 Context 无法被识别
So we need to replace it with the reference to the NumbersActivity context
我们需要将其替换为指代 NumbersActivity Context
using the syntax NumbersActivity.this.
使用语法 NumbersActivity.this
Also, Android Studio is complaining that it doesn't recognize the raw resource
此外 Android Studio 提示无法识别
called sound_file_1.
原始资源 sound_file_1
We'll need to call the sound file number_1.
我们需要将声音文件称为 number_1
So let's just update the name here.
直接更新这里的名称
Now that we can just use the name of the resource, so
我们可以直接使用资源的名称
we can leave off the name of the MP3 file extension.
不用加上 MP3 文件扩展名
All right, so after we've created the MediaPlayer object for a given sound
在为给定声音文件创建 MediaPlayer 对象后
file, we can call the start method to start playing that sound.
我们可以调用 start() 方法来开始播放声音文件
Now let's test it on our device.
现在在设备上测试下
So tap through the Numbers category and
点按 Numbers 类别
let's click on any of these list items and see if it plays the luti sound file.
点按任意一个列表项 看看是否能播放 lutti 声音文件
&gt;&gt; Luti.
lutti
&gt;&gt; Perfect.
很棒
So our app is working for our single audio file.
我们的应用可以播放单个音频文件了
Nice work.
不错